反应炉3分钟后就要爆炸
"We've got 3 minutes till it blows.
我们逃不掉了
We won't make it!"
你得赶快逃命
"You've got to get out of here! Save yourself!"
不行，我不会扔下你
"I won't leave you."
别管我
"Don't worry about me.
我是机器人，我只是一台机器
I'm a robot. I'm just a machine!"
对我来说不是
-"No,you're not. Not to me."
天哪
-Oh,my God.
怎样？ 我太有才华了
-What? -I am extremely talented.
你确实很棒
-Yeah. You're great. -Yeah.
好，我们从… 不是，我真的超会演的
-Okay,let's take it from.. -No,I mean,I was really acting my ass off.
我觉得我也很不错
I thought I was pretty good,too.
你是很不错，只不过不是我
Yeah,you're solid. You're just no me.
我看就先这样 我不想排练过头
You know what? I think that's enough for now.I don't want to be over-rehearsed.
没关系，我自己演
Fine. I'll do it without you!
我不需要你或任何人
I don't need you or anybody else!
我会靠我自己成功
I'm gonna make it on my own!
等着瞧，都给我等着瞧
You'll see! You'll all see!
本集播出：“麦克和吉事”
The One With Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
你要去试什么镜？
So what are you auditioning for?
是一部新剧集
It's a new TV show.
我的角色叫麦克麦可维利 也叫麦克
I'm up for the part of Mac,Machiavelli,or "Mac"!
我是个侦探
I'm a detective
和我的机器人拍档 一起打击犯罪
and I solve crimes with my robot partner.
他是人性化
He's a computerized humanoid...
电脑电子秘密杀手
electronically enhanced secret enforcer.
简称吉事
Or "C.H.E.E.S.E."
麦克与吉事
-So Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.?
那就是剧名
-That's the title!
幸好缩写刚好是吉事
They lucked out that the initials spell "cheese."
真是幸好
That is lucky.
要是你拿到这个角色
So Joey,if you get this,you're gonna be,like...
就有你自己的剧集了
the star of your own TV show.
你就会被称为大吉事（汉堡） 或是大麦克（麦香堡）
I mean,you'll be like the "Big Cheese" or the "Big Mac."
都是你的最爱
Hey,you love those!
别抱太大期望，应该没那么好
Don't get your hopes up. It probably won't happen.
你为什么要这么说？
Why would you say that?
拜托，我主演的影集耶？
Well,I mean,come on,guys. My own TV show?
我都不知道我配不配
-I don't know if I'm good enough.
我配
-I am
乔伊，你在说什么？ 你是个很棒的演员
What are you talking about? You're a terrific actor.
真的吗？
-You really think so?
你怎么能这么问
-How can you even ask that question?
她真漂亮
-She's pretty.
对，人也很好
-Yeah. And she's really nice too.
她教我怎么面对镜头 和闻屁演技法
She taught me all about how to work with cameras...and "smell the fart" acting.
什么？
-I'm sorry. What? -Excuse me?
因为在短时间内要背很多台词
It's like you got so many lines to learn so fast...
有时得停下来想下一句
sometimes you need time to remember your next one.
在你想的时候 要来个大停顿，表情故作严肃
So while you're thinking of it,you take this pause where you look intense.
就像这样
You know,like this:
好
Okay.
该我了该我了
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
华勒斯太太，我是雷莫瑞医生 你妹妹的神经外科医生
Mrs. Wallace? I'm Dr. Drake Ramorey,your sister's surgeon.
你妹妹得了一种…
You sister is suffering from a...
伊娃，我们有不错的进展
Well,Eva,we've done some excellent work here.
老实说，你的困扰很清楚
And I would have to say your problem is quite clear.
你只是想要一个风铃
All you want is a tinkle
你讨厌流行的东西
What you envy's a schwang
听它发出清脆的声音
A thing through which you can tinkle
拨弄着它，或是挂在那边
Or play with or simply let hang
我演艾尔帕西诺的臀部
I play Al Pacino's butt.
他走进浴室,然后... 我就是他的屁股
All right?He goes into the shower and then,I'm his butt.
天呐
-Oh,my God.
别这样，这是一部艾尔帕西诺主演大制作的电影
-Come on,you guys.This is a movie and Al Pacino's in it,and that's big!
别误会，这真是太棒了
It's terrific.
这是你应得的，这是你多年努力的成果 你终于能登上大银幕
You deserve this. After years of struggling...you've finally cracked your way into show business.
行，笑吧，我不在乎
Okay,fine,make jokes. I don't care.
这是我千载难逢的机会
This is a big break for me.
没错
-No,you're right,it is. -Yeah.
你准备邀请我们参加你的首映会吗?
So,you gonna invite us to the big opening?
好，我要走了，祝我好运
All right,I'm out of here. Wish me luck.
加油，加油，我们祝你好运
Good luck,good luck We all wish you good luck
随便啦
Yeah,whatever.
要是我会跳舞就更可怕了
Wow,if I could dance,I'd be a triple threat.
该你了
It's your turn.
我们有在玩喔？
Oh,are we playing this?
试镜结果如何？ 很烂
How'd the audition go?Terrible.
我把台词都念坏了 我不该当演员的
I messed up every word. I shouldn't even be an actor.
等等，你又在假装不顺利了吗
Wait. Are you pretending it didn't go well,but it really did go well?
对，有骗到你们吗？
-Yeah,did I fool you?
当然了
-Totally!
所以很顺利 顺利得不得了
-So it did go well? -Amazingly well!
太好了
-Great!
只剩我和另外两个人三选一 天哪
-It's down to me and two other guys.
那两个人都很厉害
And they're really good.
其中一个就是在过敏广告里 被巨无霸花朵追来追去的人
One's from those allergy commercials who's chased by flowers.
我好喜欢那个人
Oh,I love that guy!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我在干什么？
What am I doing?
我好紧张 明天下午5点才要复试
I'm so nervous,you know? The callback is tomorrow at 5:00.
我的头好像要爆炸了
-I feel like my head's gonna explode.
你的头早该爆了
-Well,it is overdue.
放心，你一定没问题
-Don't worry. You'll be fine.
压力真的好大
-But it's so much pressure.
很抱歉，但你们的工作很不同 我不知道你们能不能体会
What you guys do is different. I don't know if you'd understand.
是啊，我们的工作都没有压力
Yeah,we don't have pressure at our jobs.
我知道现在几点了 但是我对这份报告很不满意
I know what time it is,but I'm looking at the wee-ness and I'm not happy.
我在撕生菜
Well,I'm tearing the lettuce.
它脏吗？
-Is it dirty?
放心，我会洗
-Don't worry,I'll wash it.
不必，我喜欢脏的
Don't. I like it dirty.
你决定就好
That's your call.
你接下来要做什么？
So what are you going to do next?
我要切蕃茄
I thought I'd cut up the tomatoes.
它们结实吗？
Are they firm?
还不差
-They're all right.
你确定它们没有变坏？ 你确定它们没有很坏很坏？
-You sure they haven't gone bad?You sure they're not very,very bad?
它们还好
-No,really. They're okay.
你会把它们切得很漂亮吗？
-You gonna slice them real nice?
其实我想切丝
Actually,I was gonna do them julienne.
我要走了
I'm out of here.
莫妮卡，我要辞职
I'm quitting.
我帮一个老女人挤进丁字裤 结果她也没买
I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong...and she didn't even buy it.
我要辞职 我现在就要跟老板说
I'm quitting. That's it. I'm talking to my boss right now.
我要
Yes,I am.
我要我要我要…
再见，听到留言请回电
Bye. Call me when you get this message.
怎么了？
Well,what happened?
他来按摩，本来都没事 后来…
Well,he came in for a massage,and everything was fine until...
天哪
Oh,my God.
然后突然间不只是毛手毛脚
And all of a sudden,his hands weren't the problem anymore.
他有没有…
-Was it?
用来搭帐棚都绰绰有余
-Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
你吃了我的三明治？
You ate my sandwich?
很单纯的错误，谁都可能会犯
It was a mistake. It could happen to anyone.
是吗？
Really?
你别激动
Now calm down.
来我的办公室找 垃圾桶里可能还有
Come look in my office. Some of it may still be in the trash.
什么？
-What?
它很大，我只好扔掉一大半
-Well,it was quite large.I had to throw most of it away.
你…你扔掉我的三明治
You threw my sandwich away?
我的三明治
My sandwich?My sandwich!
我好想拿到这个角色
It's just,I want this part so much.
要是我没拿到
If I don't get this part,
我就再也不吃起司通心面
I'm never gonna eat macaroni and cheese again.
不，我没说，不算数
I didn't say that. That doesn't count.
别这样，我又不是搬去欧洲
Come on,guys. It's not like I moved to Europe.
我只是搬到对面
I just moved across the hall.
我们也想经常请你们来坐 但是莫妮卡会过敏
And we would have you over all the time...if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
没错，我骗不了你们
You're right,I could never lie to you.
她讨厌你们
She hates you.
要接吗？
Should I get that?
你好
Hello?
乔伊现在不在，你要留言吗？
No,Joey's not here right now. Can I take a message?
好，试镜从5点改到2点半？
Yeah,okay. So the audition's been moved from 5:00 to 2:30?
好的，再见
Okay,great. Bye.
你还没穿衣服？
-Aren't you dressed yet?
我又光着身体了？
-Am I naked again?
我们15分钟后要去见我爸妈
We're meeting my parents in 15 minutes.
好，我只是在跟它们聊天
I was just talking to the guys.
你看它们嘛 它们可以去找我们吗？
Look at them.Is it okay if they come visit?
那我的过敏怎么办？
What about my allergies?
也对，你会过敏
Right. Your allergies.
都是她，她讨厌你们
All her. She hates you.
漂亮
Yes! All right.
要是这些小人能变成真人大小 该有多酷？
How cool would it be if you could watch a life-size version of this?
该有多过瘾？
-I mean,how crazy would that be?
跟真实的足球一样过瘾？
-As crazy as soccer?
你好
Hello?
你在说什么？5点才试镜
What are you talking about? The audition's at 5.
没有人告诉我，你跟谁说的？
Well,nobody told me.Who'd you talk to?
没事
Never mind.
这样你看不懂吗？
You mean you didn't get it from this?
那个过敏人入选了，谢谢你啊
-The allergy guy got the part. Thanks.
也许还可以补救 我们可以送巨无霸花去吓他
-Maybe we can fix it.Maybe we can send him some big flowers and scare him!
你怎么能这样？ 这个角色可以让我的事业翻红
How could you do this? This could've turned my career around.
是我不好
I messed up,okay?
对不起，我真的错了
I'm sorry. I really messed up.
你根本也不住这里了 干嘛接我的电话？我有答录机
Why'd you answer my phone?I have a machine!
是我买给你的
-Which I bought for you.
还教你怎么使用
Taught you how to use it.
你以为它是影印机
You thought it was a copier.
我愿意尽全力挽救这个错误
If there was anything I could do,I'd do it.
但是人起码可以犯一次错
Everybody's allowed one mistake,right?
他可以送我录影机 可以送我高尔夫球具
He could have gotten me a VCR or golf clubs.
可是他偏偏要让我把女人吓跑
But no,he has to get me the "Woman Repeller."
一个废五金行里最丑的东西
The eyesore from the "Liberace House of Crap!"
没那么严重
-It's not that bad.
你又不必戴着 被某个老粗淘汰的金饰到处跑
-Easy for you to say.You don't have to sport a reject from the "Mr. T" collection.
钱德，钱德
Chandler
“我真同情戴这个手饰的人” “真的”
I pity the fool who puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!
“我真同情戴这个…” 你好
I pity the fool that...
你昨天晚归 凯西和我聊了起来
When you were late last night,Kathy and I were talking and...
事情演变到后来就…
one thing led to another and....
就什么？你跟她上床？
And what? Did you sleep with her?
没有，我只是吻了她
-No! No,I just kissed her.
什么？那样更糟！
-What? That's even worse!
怎么会更糟？ 我不知道，反正都一样
-How? -I don't know! But it's the same!
你说得对，我无话可说 我太过分了
I have no excuses. I was over the line.
过分？你根本就过分到
Over the line?You're so far past the line you can't even see it!
连过分见到你都会说你过分
The line is a dot to you!
我不是要你奇迹式的原谅我
I'm not saying you should magically forgive me.
但你也不完美 你也做过错误的判断
But you're not perfect. You've made errors in judgment.
举个例子
Name one!
怎么回事？
What happened?
他答应不拿沙发椅的
Man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!
怎么回事？你怎么会被关进去 我们的东西呢？
How were you locked in? And where the hell's all of our stuff?
有一个人来看柜子 他说它塞不下一个大人
This guy came to look at the unit...and he didn't think it was big enough to fit a man.
所以你就自愿进去？
So you got in voluntarily?
我想把柜子卖出去
I was trying to make a sale!
要是让我碰上他 你猜我会怎样？
If I ever run into him again,know what I'll do?
把屁股翘起来？
Bend over?
她来了
There's Lori.
记住，不准交换
Remember,no trading.
美女是你的，失恋女是我的
You get the pretty one,I get the mess.
乔伊
-Hi,Joey. -Hey.
他就是你带来的人
Well,well. Look what you brought.
你又带了谁来？
And what did you bring?
她在放外套
She's checking her coat.
乔伊，我要去洗个手
Joey,I'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands.
你帮我叫一杯白酒 帮珍妮丝叫一杯红酒
Will you get me a white Zinfandel and a glass of red for Janice.
珍妮丝？珍妮丝？
Janice?
我…的…天哪
Oh,my God!
乔伊的裁缝占我便宜
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
什么？
What?
不可能 我找他做了12年衣服
No way. I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
拜托啦，他说要量裤管内侧
You said he'd do my inseam...
然后他的手一路摸上来 然后就…
then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was...
怎样？
What?
包住了
Cupping.
裤子就是那样量的
That's how they do pants!
罗斯，你告诉他 裤子不都是那样量的吗？
-Isn't that how a tailor measures?
是啊是啊…在监狱里
-Yes,yes,it is. In prison!
叫你举一个就好
I said name one!
我居然这么粗心，我真白痴
-I can't believe I did this.
别再自责了
-Stop beating yourself up.
人都会犯错，这是难免的
People make mistakes. These things happen.
你没有忘记帮我记留言吧？
There aren't any messages you've forgotten to give me?
很明显，你不擅长这项工作
Apparently,you're not very good at it.
你们觉得他会原谅我吗？
-Do you think he'll forgive me?
当然会，但最重要的是 你得原谅自己
-Of course.The important thing is that you forgive yourself.
其实我已经原谅自己了
-You know what,I kind of have.
这么快？你犯的错蛮严重的
-Already?That was pretty bad what you did.
他会原谅你的
He will forgive you.
我接电话时都会带便条纸… 好啦
I like to bring a pad with me when I answer the phone,okay?
你没看到他气成什么样子
-You didn't see how mad he was.
他一定会原谅你的 我们都有这种经验
-I'm sure he'll forgive you.We've all been there.
吵架，和解，就是这样
You fight,you make up. That's how it works.
这段感情会破裂是两个人的错
It took two people to break up this relationship!
对，你和影印店那个女的 你昨天表明愿意负责
Yeah! You and that copy girl...which yesterday you took responsibility for!
我不知道我负的是什么责
I didn't know what I was taking responsibility for.
我没把信看完
-I didn't finish the letter.
什么？ 我睡着了
-What?-I fell asleep.
你睡着了？
-You fell asleep?
当时是早上5点半
It was 5:30 in the morning.
你一废话就废话了十八页
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
正反面都写满了
Front and back!
还有 “You”后面加ER是指“你是”
And by the way? Y-O-U,apostrophe R-E means,"you are."
“Y-O-U-R”是指“你的”
Y-O-U-R means "your."
我居然会想跟你复合 我们根本就完了
I can't believe I thought of getting back together with you.We are so over!
无所谓
Fine by me!
顺便告诉你
And just so you know,
那种事并不常见 并非男人都会那样
it's not that common...it doesn't happen to every guy,
那是很严重的
and it is a big deal!
我就知道
I knew it!
你没有权利和他约会
-You had no right to go out with him.
这真是太荒谬…
-That's ridiculous..
你出卖我 我没有出卖你
-You sold me out! -I did not!
让我说话好吗？
-You did! You sold me.. -Would you let me talk?
你弹我的额头吗？
Did you just flick me?
你不让我说完，我很…
Well,you wouldn't let me finish and..
好，不要这样
-All right. No,let's not do this. -No!
想想快乐的事
-Happy thoughts. -No!
好，我要发威了
Okay,now I'm gonna kick some ass!
你们住手，我就放手
All right. Now,I will let go if you both stop.
好吧
-Fine. -Fine.
这不就结了
There we go.
如果我们在坐牢 你们就是我的婆娘
You know what? If we were in prison,you guys would be my bitches.
兄弟，如何啊
Okay,buddy boy,here it is.
你藏我的衣服 我就穿你全部的衣服
You hide my clothes? I'm wearing everything you own.
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
看啊，我是钱德 我穿的衣服够多吧？
Look at me,I'm Chandler! Could I be wearing any more clothes?
也许我没有穿内裤
Maybe if I wasn't going commando.
穿这么多衣服真热
I tell you,it's hot with all this on.
我最好别做弓箭步
I'd better not do any lunges.
乔伊？
Joey?
我买了欢乐套餐，有两个披萨
Got you the Joey special! Two pizzas!
乔伊？
Joey
你好
Hello?
又来了
Damn it!
你好
Hello?
乔伊现在不在 我可以帮你留言…应该吧
No,Joey's not here right now,but I can take a message. I think.
他还有机会？真是太好了
He's still got a chance for the part? That's great news!
我不是说那位被狗咬伤的演员
Well,no,obviously not for the actor who was mauled by his dog.
太好了，我会转告乔伊，谢谢
That's great. I'll give Joey the message.
漂亮
Yes!
好，麦克…试镜…2点钟
Okay.Mac...audition...at 2:00.
过敏…演员…遭攻击
Allergy...actor...attacked.
被狗…不是…被花
By dog...not...flowers.
请告诉我你有收到留言
-Tell me you got the message.
什么留言？
-What message?
要演麦克的演员不能演 他们要你2点过去
The actor playing Mac couldn't do it. They needed you at 2.
什么？明明是6点
What? It's 6:00!
我有写在留言板上
Look! I wrote it on the board!
我写在留言板上 然后跑遍整个纽约找你
I wrote it down,then went looking for you!
我跑去罗斯家，跑去咖啡馆 跑去每一个有三明治的地方
I went to Ross's,the coffee house...I went to any place they make sandwiches!
真不敢相信，钱德
-I can't believe this,Chandler!
对不起，我不知道该说什么
-I'm sorry.I don't know what to say!
那就说恭喜吧
-You might say congratulations!
我看到留言板，跑去试镜 我中了
I saw the board,I went to the audition,I got the part!
你觉得很好笑吗？ 我刚才真的很担心
Was that funny? I was worried.
有时候这样骗人真的很恶劣
-I'm sorry. -That fake-out thing is just mean.
抱歉，我不是故意要害你内疚
Oh,I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
那就好
Well,that's good.
因为我没有内疚 我好替你高兴
Because you didn't! And I'm incredibly happy for you!
你好恶劣
That's mean!
你害我惭愧
-You had me going!
再玩下去就没完没了了 也对
-We could do this all day.Yeah,you're right.
好，我们来聊聊我会有多红
Let's talk about what a huge star I'm gonna be.
你会变成超级大明星
You're gonna be huge! I'm gonna hug you!
我要抱你 来抱吧
-You hug me! -All right.
我们会不会太爱抱了？ 我也觉得
-Do we do this too much? -I think so.
放开我 是啊
-Yeah. Get off me. -Yeah.
吉事，我不会扔下你的
"C.H.E.E.S.E.,I'm not leaving without you.
你从中央处理器 启动备用电源
Route your backup power source through your CPU."
没办法，我的电路烧焦了 焦到不能再焦
"l can't! My circuits are fried! They're fried,I tell you!"
那我就背你
"Then I'll carry you!"
好棒的招数啊 等你死了再说
"That'll be a neat trick...""when you're dead!"
罗斯，你不必用喊的
You don't have to yell.
刚才有爆炸，我的听力会受损
There was just an explosion. My hearing would be impaired.
我觉得你很棒
I thought you were great.
刚才我甚至觉得“罗斯怎么还不出场？”
For a minute,I was like,"Where'd Ross go?"
谢谢 你和麦克见面的第一场戏…
Thank you. And that first scene where you meet Mac...
怎样？ 我的天哪
-Yeah? -Oh,my God. I mean...
今天就到此为止，多谢帮忙
And you know what?That's enough for today. Thanks for your help.
他拖我们后腿了 就是啊
-Holding us back. -Totally.